Guide to the Burton Hall Papers WAG.087
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Union Democracy Cases, 67652
  - Subseries H: Unions (arrangement - alphabetical), 67653
    - NATIONAL RURAL LETTER CARRIERS ASSOCIATION (NRLCA); Briggs, William v. Letter Carriers & U.S. Postal Service; Correspondence, Jan 27, 1986; Notice of Deposition (for), Dec 21, 1987, 1986, 1987; 67677 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, W. Sloan, Jan 7, 1988; Postal Service Documents, 67676 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 89-6275; Appellate Briefs; Petition for Rehearing (BH), undated; 67675 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - BROTHERHOOD OF RAILWAY CLERKS (BRAC); Includes "The Railway Clerk's Voice", undated; 67674 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - RETAIL, WHOLESALE DEPARTMENT STORE UNION (RWDSU), Local 1001, NLRB 1980, 67673 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Local 1102 - RWDSU; Woodberry, Warren (Discharge), 1980-1982, 67672 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Local 88 - RWDSU; Stewart, Edmund; NLRB - Mendon Leasing, 1979-1981, 67671 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Local 88 - Mendon Leasing, 1981-1982, 67670 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - SERVICE EMPLOYEES INTERNATIONAL UNION (SEIU), Local 144, Hotel, Hospital, Nursing Home & Allied Health Services Union, SEIU; Easley, Charles v. Ottley, Peter J., President, Local 144, 1977, 67669 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Local 32 B - 32 J, SEIU; Whittaker, Cedric; NLRB - Columbia University, undated; 67667 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - UPHOLSTERERS, DECORATORS & ALLIED CRAFTS, Local 44, Roman, Louis; 72 Civ. 4600; NLRB Correspondence, May 27, 1971; Complaint, Whitney North Seymour, Jr., U.S. Attorney, Oct 26, 1972; James D. Hodgson, Secretary, Department of Labor v. Local 44, Upholsterers (Title IV - L-MRDA), 1971, 1972; 67666 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Stipulation, Nov 17, 1972; Reply Affidavit, Dec 20, 1973, 1972, 1973; 67665 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Affidavit, BH, Jan, 1974; Affidavit, L. Roman, Oct, 1974, 67664 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 77 Civ. 0891 (CBM); Roman, L. v. United Exposition Service Co. Inc.; Index; Judicial Ruling, Charles M. Metzner, D.J., Dec 12, 1977, 67663 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Je 16, 1978; Correspondence, BH, Nov 29, 1978, 67662 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Feb 7, 1979; Correspondence, Oct 3, 1979, 67661 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Pre-Trial Order, Oct 5, 1979; Judicial Order (Metzner), Dec 5 1979, 67660 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission; (EEOC) Documents - L. Roman, undated; 67658 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - New York State Division on Human Rights - Documents - L. Roman, undated; 67657 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Plaintiff's Exhibits; Joint Exhibits, undated; 67656 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - UTILITY WORKERS OF AMERICA, Local 1-2; Correspondence, 1980, 67654 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Series III: Employment Discrimination, 67649
  Series III consists of legal files related to employment discrimination cases.
  - Canty, Seth (all), 1978-1981; 67650 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Pan Am Equities, Inc., 1981 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Employment Discrimination Research File, 1977-1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Schifano, Charlotte, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Rhoda, 1979-1981 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Watson, Jeptha B., 1982 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Unidentified Librarian, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Series IV: Photographs
  The photographs include images of a 1962 protest in Times Square organized by the War Resisters League, portraits of Burton Hall, and a photograph of Paul Pisman after his assault.
  - Anti-Atomic Bomb Peace Demonstration (War Resisters League), March 1962; 465214 (Box A001, Folder 1)
  - Hall, Burton, 1979, undated; 465215 (Box A001, Folder 2)
  - Pisman, Paul, circa 1961; 465216 (Box A001, Folder 3)
- Series V: 2007-2008 accretion, 438693
  Series V contains case files and legal documents including: affidavits, depositions, motions, District Court and appellate briefs, exhibits, appendices, court transcripts. Cases found in this series address various union disputes and date mostly from the late 1970s to the early 1990s. Major cases found in this series include The Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530; Drywall Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, Circle Industries, Component Assembly Systems, Inc., Bernie Wolff Construction, Co.; Petramale v. Local 17 & Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA); and Rodonich et. al. v. House Wreckers Union Local 95 of LIUNA, LIUNA, et. al.
  More detailed notes outlining the principal cases in this series and the types of documents in each casefile can be found in the detailed inventory on file.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Some materials (Box 39, Box 51A) have been moved to quarantine in July 2017 due to mold and may not be accessible to researchers.
  As of October 2017 Box 56 is missing.
  - Petramale v. Local 17 & LIUNA (LMRDA case), 1980s (Box 28)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CV-0337) (injunction case), 1984-1988 (Box 28)
  - Tapers Trustees (Local 1974) v. Component Assembly, 1980s (Box 28)
  - Petramale v. Local 17 & LIUNA, 1980s (Box 29)
  - Petramale v. Local 17 & LIUNA, 1980s-1993 (Box 30)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 81-CIV-0337, 1985-1991 (Box 31)
  - Drywall Tapers and Charles Long v. Operative Plasterers, 75-CV-4289, 78-7352 and 76-7108, 1970s (Box 31)
  - Alfarone v. Nastasi White, et al. (84-CIV-3181), 1984-1985 (Box 31)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1990 (Box 32)
  - Alfarone v. Nastasi White, et al. Case numbers 84-CIV-3181, 84-CIV-4028, 1978-1990 (Box 32)
  - De Rosa v. Blank, et al, 1970s (Box 32)
  - Improved Drywall v. Teamsters Local 272, 1984 (Box 32)
  - Mixed: early Drywall Tapers' Funds cases and jurisdictional dispute cases, circa 1990 (Box 33)
  - Alfarone v. Standard Drywall: Case # CV-81-015, circa 1990 (Box 34)
  - Alfarone, etc., et al. v. Nastasi White, etc., et al.: Case # 85-7899, 1979-2004 (Box 34)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974' Funds v. Nastasi White: Case # 91-CIV-0650, 1990 (Box 34)
  - Alfarone v. Standard Drywall: Case # CV-81-015, 1980s (Box 34)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: Case # 81-CIV-0337, 1987-1990 (Box 34)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: Case # 81-CIV-0337, 1982-1989 (Box 35)
  - Drywall Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White: Case # 91-CIV-0650, 1990 (Box 36)
  - US v. Mason Tenders District Council, 1994 (Box 36)
  - State of NY v. John F. O'Connor, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Local 1974 Funds v. Bernie Wolff Construction et al, etc. 91-CIV-0634, etc., 1991 (Box 36)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (Case # 81-CIV-0337), 1985 (Box 36)
  - Drywall Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White (Case # 91-CIV-0650), 1991 (Box 36)
  - People v. Bitondo and Hanley, 1990 (Box 36)
  - People v. O'Hara, undated (Box 36)
  - US v. Anthony "Fat Tony" Salerno, Vincent Dinapoli, "Fish" Cafaro, et al., Circa 1986 (Box 36)
  - Drywall Tapers' Funds case, 1995 (Box 36)
  - Petramale v. Local 17 and LIUNA, 1983; 1987 (Box 37)
  - Turner v. Air Transport Lodge of IAM and IAM, etc., Circa 1978 (Box 37)
  - BTEA (Building Trades Employers' Association) Arbitration Transcript, 1991 (Re: Plasterers' Local 60/Painters' D.C. 9) (Box 37)
  - Tapers Trustees v. Nastasi White, et. al., 1991 (Box 37)
  - Tapers v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s-early 1990s (Box 37)
  - Tapers and Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1970s (Box 37)
  - Putterman v. Knitwear, etc., 1973-1976 (Box 37)
  - Painters' DC9 Journal/Yearbook (1943) (Box 37)
  - Eatz v. NYRA, 91-9161 and 63, 1992 (Box 37)
  - Trustees v. Employer Trustees (Drywall Tapers), Circa 1985-1990 (Box 37)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1989-1992 (Box 37)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s-early 1990s (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Jones v. Operative Plasterers, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Clay v. Castle Coal and Oil, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Rodonich v. Local 95 and LIUNA, 1986 (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Trustees v. Bernie Wolff Construction et. al., 1980s (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1979 (Box 38)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 84-7137, 1980s (Box 39)
  - Alfarone, etc. and Drywall Tapers Fund Trustees v. Bernie Wolff Construction et. al., 1986 (Box 39)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1970s (Box 39)
  - Alfarone, et. al. V. Bernie Wolff et al., 1985 (Box 39)
  - Rodonich v. Housewreckers Union Local 95 and LIUNA, 1986,1994 (Box 40)
  - Alfarone v. Bernie Wolff, etc. et. al., 1973-1989 (Box 40)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s-1990s (Box 40)
  - Eric Frankland v. IAPE, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Plimack v. Nolan and NABET, 85 Civ. 4668 (Judge: LB Sand)(LMRDA case challenging retaliation against Plimack, a former NABET officer), Circa 1983-1985 (Box 41)
  - Lynn Bell (Bakery, etc. Workers' Union), Circa 1970s-1980s (Box 41)
  - Burton Hall's Bar Admission Certificates (1951, 1960s, 1985) (Box 41)
    Some certificates moved to Quarantine box 51A due to mold in July 2017.
  - Ralph Clay v. Castle Coal and Oil, Dept. Of Labor Case No. 90-STA-00037:(OSHA case by TDU member discharged for complaining about unsafe working conditions), Early 1990s (Box 42)
  - BTEA hearing transcripts, June 24, 1980, in Tapers and Plasterers jurisdictional dispute between Drywall Tapers Local 1974 & Plasterers Local 530 (Box 43)
  - The New York Plan for the Settlement of Jurisdictional Disputes, 1976 (Box 43)
  - Deposition transcripts: Tapers and Long v. Plasterers Int'l., 1976-1982 (Box 43)
  - Deposition Transcripts: De Rosa v. Blank (Drywall Tapers), 1977 (Box 43)
  - Deposition Transcripts: Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1982 (Box 43)
  - Deposition Transcripts: John Alfarone, et al. v. Standard Drywall Corp, et al., 1981-1982 (Box 43)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1982-1989 (Box 44)
  - US v. District Council of Carpenters (related organized crime prosecution), 1990 (Box 44)
  - State of NY v. Moscatiello, 1995 (Box 44)
  - John Alfarone et al. v. Nastasi-White, Inc., et al.: CV 84-3181, 1984 (Box 44)
  - Drywall Tapers Funds collections cases, Circa 1984-1985 (Box 44)
  - Plimack v. Nolan (85-CIV-4668), 1983-1985 (Box 44)
  - US v. District Council of Carpenters (90-CIV-5722), 1993 (Box 45)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff...) (91-CIV- 0650, etc.), 1996 (Box 45)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1980s (Box 45)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1970s-1980s (Box 45)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council: Pertinent jurisdictional dispute documents, 1970s-1980s (Box 45)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1990 (Box 46)
  - Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White et al., 1980s (Box 46)
  - Putterman v. Knitgoods Workers Union, et al. (including ILGWU) (78 CIV 8000), Circa 1980s (Box 46)
  - Plimack v. Nolan and NABET, 85 Civ. 4668 (Judge: LB Sand), 1980s (Box 46)
  - Wall, et al. v. Construction and General Laborers Union, Local 230, et al., 1997-1998 (Box 46)
  - Pamphlet: Amalgamated Lithographers Local 1: By-laws, July 1974 (Box 46)
  - Pamphlet: Some Sample Provisions for Collective Bargaining Agreements: For the Guidance of Affiliates of the International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, AFL-CIO, 1970s (Box 47)
  - Pamphlet: NY State Department of Labor, 1960 (Box 47)
  - Trade Union Courier, June 1981 (Box 47)
  - Pamphlet: International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots Analysis of Labor-Management Relations Problems, June 1966 (Box 47)
  - Report: US House of Representatives Investigation of the Civil Rights Enforcement Activities of the Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs, US Dept. of Labor, May 1987 (Box 47)
  - Article: Bureau of National Affairs, "House Subcommittee Report on Labor Cites Growing Politicization of NLRB", 1984 (Box 47)
  - New Politics, Vol. IX, No. 3, January 1972 (Box 47)
  - Libertarian Analysis, Vol. 1 No. 4, December 1971 (Box 47)
  - National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, AFL-CIO, 1960 (Box 47)
  - National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 47)
  - US v. Bonanno Organized Crime Family of La Cost Nostra, et al, 1987 (Box 47)
  - US v. International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots International Maritime Division, 1972 (Box 47)
  - Confidential Memorandum Concerning Powell-Nazden Efforts to Clean up the Laborers' Union, August 1982 (Box 47)
  - Rosario, Vega and Cabel v. Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10 ILGWU, et al., 1984 (Box 47)
  - AFL-CIO Lawyers' Conference papers on public employees' rights, May 1982 (Box 47)
  - Earl Lucas v. Western Union International: NY City Commission on Human Rights, 1981-1989 (Box 47)
  - Drywall Tapers Contempt Litigation, June 1984 (Box 47)
  - Federal Labor Relations Authority Region II: Bureau of Labor Statistics, NY Region and National Council of Field Labor Locals, American Federation of Government Employees, AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 47)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 (82-CIV-5583), 1983-1985 (Box 48)
  - Santos v. District Council, 1979 (Box 49)
  - Petramale v. LIUNA, 1983; 1987 (Box 49)
  - Union Trustees v. Employer Trustees (Drywall Tapers), 1983-1989 (Box 49)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s (Box 49)
  - Ted Kozera & RIchard M. Mekeel etc. et al. v. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, eta al, 1993 (Box 49)
  - Taper's Trustees v Nastasi-White et al (Bernie Wolff ... ) (91 Civ. 0650, etc.), 1981-1995 (Box 50)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff), 1982; 1993-1996 (Box 51)
  - Eatz v. DME United of Local 3 & The New York Racing Association, 1960s; 1980s (Box 51A)
  - Tapers v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 89-7127: petition for re-hearing, Circa 1989 (Box 51A)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530: 91-7153: supplemental index, v. 3, 1980s-1990s (Box 51A)
  - Burton Hall's Bar Admission Certificates, 1951, 1960s, 1985 (Box 51A)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s; 1995 (Box 52)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Charles Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1975 (Box 52)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 and Charles Long v. Operative Plasterers, 1978 (Box 52)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff), 1980s-1990s (Box 52)
  - John Alfarone v. Standard Drywall, 1982 (Box 53)
  - James Ricks v. American Radio Association, 1981 (Box 53)
  - John Alfarone v. Standard Drywall, 1984 (Box 53)
  - New York Times article: June 28, 1989, p. B4. "Grand Jury Vote Expected Soon in Union Inquiry," (Box 53)
  - US v. District Council of Carpenters, 1992 (Box 53)
  - Trustees of the Tapers' Funds v. Nastasi White, et al. (Component Assembly, Bernie Wolff), 1990s (Box 53)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530, 1980s (Box 53)
  - Rodonich et al. v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA, 1980-1989 (Box 54)
  - Rodonich, Joseph, et al. v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA, 1981; 1986 (Box 55)
  - Rodonich-related: Raymond Donovan (US Secretary of Labor) and US Department of Labor and Rodonich, et al. v. House Wreckers' Union Local 95 of LIUNA, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Rodonich-related: NRLB charges re: Local 95 hiring hall practices, 1985 (Box 55)
  - John Hayes, Masters Mates & Pilots, 1986-1987 (Box 55)
  - Putterman v. Knitgoods Workers Union, et al. (including ILGWU) (78-Civ-6000, early 1980s (Box 55)
  - Petramale v. LIUNA (81-4817), 1980s (Box 55)
  - Drywall Tapers and Long, etc. v. Plasterers (75-CIV-4289) (Judge Metzner), Circa 1975-1979 (Box 57)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1980s (Box 57)
  - Alfarone et al v. Standard Drywall (81-CIV-0151). (Judge Bramwell), Early 1980s (Box 57)
  - Arbitration Between Union-Appointed Trustees of the Tapers Industry Insurance and Annuity Funds and Employer-Appointed Trustees of the Tapers Industry Insurance and Annuity Funds, 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - Louis Caputo v. Solomon Salzhandler (US Supreme Court case no. 282), 1963 (Box 57)
  - Arbitration between Drywall Tapers and National Wall, Circa 1973 (Box 57)
  - Donovan v. Kaszycki 82 Civ 3287, 1982-1983 (Box 57)
  - Drywall Tapers Local 1974 v. Operative Plasterers Local 530 (81-CIV-0337), 1975-1984 (Box 57)
  - Alfarone, et al. v. Standard Drywall, et al. (81-CIV-0151), 1981 (Box 57)
  - Louis Caputo, President of NY DC 9 of Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, et al. v. Solomon Salzhandler, October 1963 (Box 57)
  - Max Sands, as Administrator of the Estate of Solomon Salzhandler v. Louis Caputo (President of DC 9, Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers of America), et al., 1967 (Box 58)
  - Samuel Winn v. Martin Rarback, 1961 (Box 58)
  - French v. Rarback, 1961 (Box 58)
  - Petramale v. LIUNA (81-4817), 1980s-1992 (Box 58)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1982 (Box 58)
  - Kozera et. al. V. Westchester-Fairfiled Chapter of the National Electrical Contractors Association, et. al., 1988 (Box 58)
  - Kozera et al. v. IBEW et. al., 1992-1994 (Box 58)
  - Putterman vs. ILGWU, Circa 1978 (Box 59)
  - Rodonich vs. Housewreckers and LIUNA, 1980s - 1990s (Box 59)
  - Kozera 1 (Kozera et al v. Westchester-Fairfield Chapter), 1989 (Box 59)
  - Kozera 2 ( (Kozera vs IBEW), 1995 (Box 59)
  - Petramale vs Local 17 and LIUNA, 1992 (Box 59)
  - Demolition Industry contractors and associates: criminal charges and complaints, 1988 (Box 59)
  - Newspaper clippings related to Rodonich case and LIUNA, 1970s-1980s (Box 59)
  - Wall and Cooksey v. Construction Laborer's Local 230, 1999 (Box 60)
  - Drywall Tapers: 2nd Circuit Appeal Briefs, 1984 (Box 60)
  - Drywall Tapers: Funds Case, 1989;1991 (Box 60)
  - Earl Lucas, et al. v. MCI Communications Corp, et al. (83 Civ. 2727), 1975-1988 (Box 60)
  - Related NLRB charges and decisions, undated (Box 60)
  - Joetta Winfield v WUI (87 Civ. 5901), 1987 (Box 60)
  - Earl Lucas and Trudy Seraneau v. WUI et al (88 Civ. 0862), 1988 (Box 60)
  - Arthur Steier v WUI (81 Civ. 4677 and 81-7848), 1981 (Box 60)
  - Earl Lucas v. Western Union International, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1970s-1990s (Box 61)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1978-1987 (Box 62)
  - Kozera vs IBEW, 1995 (Box 62)
  - Kozera et al v. Westchester-Fairfield Chapter, et al. 89-9072, 1989 (Box 62)
  - Max Sands v. Louis Caputo, 1967 (Box 62)
  - Sheldon v. O'Callaha, 1970 (Box 62)
  - Alfarone vs. Bernie Wolff, 1986 (Box 62)
  - Kozera v. Westchester Fairfield Chapter of National Electrical Contractors Association, Inc. (87 Civ. 5540), 1988 (Box 63)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Union Annuity and Pension Funds v. Nastasi-White, Inc et al. (91 Civ. 0650), 1981-1996 (Box 64)
  - Legal documents and decisions in John Alfarone as Trustee, et al v. Albee Drywall Partitions, Inc. (81 Civ. 1056) Predecessor Case, 1981 (Box 64)
  - Rodonich v. Local 95 & LIUNA, 1978-1985 (Box 64)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 & LIUNA, 1981 (Box 65)
  - Foreword and Introduction to "The Impact: Organized Crime Today.", April 1986 (Box 65)
  - Draft complaint of US v. LIUNA et al, undated (Box 65)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1981-1983 (Box 66)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 67)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1970s-1980s (Box 68)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 69)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 70)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 71)
  - Settlement in NLRB case: Chotowicky and Diduck vs. Local 95, charge number 2-CB-9548 (Union Hiring Hall System), undated (Box 71)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95 of LIUNA and LIUNA (82-CIV-5583), 1970s-1980s (Box 72)
  - Transcript of Criminal Trial in US v Joseph Sherman, McNair & Roshetski (84 Cr. 205), undated (Box 72)
  - Drywall Tapers v. Local 530 (CV-81-337), 1985, 1990 (Box 73)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Insurance, Annuity and Pension Funds v. Nastasi White, Bernie Wolff Construction et al., 1990s (Box 73)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1977-1980 (Box 74)
  - Rodonich v. House Wreckers Local 95, 1981-1982 (Box 75)
  - Trustees of the Tapers Insurance, Annuity and Pension Funds v. Nastasi White, Bernie Wolff Construction et al., 1980s-1990s (Box 76)
  - Unlabelled photographs [moved from box 44], undated (Box 77)
  - Cassette tape: "trail @ NABET" [moved from box 41], 1983 (Box 77)